FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 9, Thu Duc City HCMC 0938863878 nghia.nvt291@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Developer with 3 years of experience in Laravel Framework. I always ready to learn new technologies. High responsibility. Good at teamwork. Good at reading and listening English. Ability to do both Back-End and Front-End development.

RELEVANT SKILL

PHP 8/LARAVEL 9 JQUERY/JAVASCRIPT HTML - CSS - BOOTSTRAP 5

REST API – AJAX MY SQL/DESIGN DATABASE GIT/GITLAB/GITHUB DESIGN PATTERN

JIRA – FIGMA APACHE / FILEZILLA NODE JS (BASIC)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end developer

Lot Technology LLC JAN 2023 - NOW

Project: NIFEHUB.COM

- Troubleshoot bugs exists pages/functions
- Support team (technical, fixing bugs ...).
- Connect with Speedsize: Al-optimize website with neuroscience to optimize video, images fast loading.
- · Connect with Gov.com.vn to show our datas for government.

Project: NIFEBUSINESS.COM (CRM)

- Making source and clone theme metronic to serve our web business.
- To do module with make Apis and also do front-end.
- Scraping website (fb, ins, tiktok, ytb) get total user followers, user followings, likes, username...
- Setting schedules to run scraping website.
- Troubleshoot bugs.
- Support clients.
- Support technical for CS.

Project: NIFEHUB APP

- Support team app (technical, logics ...).
- Making notifications, send email using queues.
- Making api send sms, connect with Vietguys.
- Connect with nganluong for payment.
- Making apis for app calling.
- Maintained exist apis.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 9, Thu Duc City HCMC 0938863878 nghia.nvt291@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Developer with 3 years of experience in Laravel Framework. I always ready to learn new technologies. High responsibility. Good at teamwork. Good at reading and listening English. Ability to do both Back-End and Front-End development.

RELEVANT SKILL

PHP 8/LARAVEL 9 JQUERY/JAVASCRIPT HTML - CSS - BOOTSTRAP 5

REST API – AJAX MY SQL/DESIGN DATABASE GIT/GITLAB/GITHUB DESIGN PATTERN

JIRA – FIGMA APACHE / FILEZILLA NODE JS (BASIC)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end developer

Lot Technology LLC JAN 2023 - NOW

Project: CMS.NIFEHUB.COM/BACKEND (CMS)

- Support/ Custom/ CRUD modules.
- Troubleshoot bugs.
- Support technical for CS.
- Making agencies managements, identities, setting email templates, notification templates ...
- Maintaince modules.

Project: NIFEHUB BOOKING

- Making source
- Making apis login

TECHICAL SKILLS

 Php 8/Laravel 9, OctoberCms, Apache, Xampp, Design Pattern, Jquery, Javascript, Html, Twig, Css, Bootstrap 5, Figma, Jira, Restful Api, Mysql, Heidi Sql, Workbench Sql, Design Database, Github, Filezilla, Support technical

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 9, Thu Duc City HCMC 0938863878 nghia.nvt291@gmail.com

PROFILE SUMMARY

Developer with 3 years of experience in Laravel Framework. I always ready to learn new technologies. High responsibility. Good at teamwork. Good at reading and listening English. Ability to do both Back-End and Front-End development.

RELEVANT SKILL

PHP/LARAVEL JQUERY/JAVASCRIPT HTML - CSS BOOTSTRAP 5

REST API MY SQL/DESIGN DATABASE GIT/GITLAB/GITHUB DESIGN PATTERN

JIRA - FIGMA APACHE AJAX

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end developer

IHOUZZ TECHNOLOGY JOINT STOCK COMPANY

May 2022 - Dec 2022

Project: Ihouzz product

- Make new version for homepage, maintained product page, and another pages.
- · Maintained filter using laravel livewire.
- Maintained another pages to ensure high traffic, page views, and user experience
- Review and clean code.
- Maintained Apis facebook messenger.

Project: Ihouzz cms

- Support team to create/update pages content for ihouzz product website.
- Fix bugs

Project: Ihouzz api

- Support create/update apis and maintain exists api.
- Participate, discuss with team leader to design and make new table in database.

Project: Ihouzz crm

- Troubleshoot bugs exists pages/functions in Ihouzz crm website.
- Make activity logs of employees.
- To do a command to make repository pattern
- To do validate function using laravel validation.

TECHICAL SKILLS

• Php/Laravel, Apache, Xampp, Design Pattern, Jquery, Html, Css, Bootstrap 5, Figma, Jira, Restful Api, Mysql, Heidi Sql, Design Database, Git, Bitbucket.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 9, Thu Duc City HCMC +0938863878 | nghia.nvt291@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end Developer

CLOUD TEAM COMPANY LIMITED

May 2019 - May 2022

Project Chanel Cleareance CRM

- To do modules about import/export products to xlsx/csv file using queues.
- To do modules to show products follow customer proposed.

Project Ryco Package Crm

- To do modules items, customers, categories etc.
- Troubleshoot modules.
- To do send email follow request of team leader.

Project Louis Vuilton Crm

- Generates invoices to pdf file using mpdf.
- To do modules and troubleshoot modules.
- Verify XML, Invoice pdf file.
- To do Apis to get datas.

Project Louis Vuilton Portal - Project Chanel Portal (Solo Projects)

- To do show information/ content about customer's company.
- To do page to filter invoices by secret code.
- To do page to verify xml files to show invoices.

Project Jinhye Wordpress - Project Jinhye Shop - Project Kaspersky CRM

- To do Landing page, Signin/Signup pages, profile page etc.
- To do send email to confirm new account, new phone.
- Troubleshoot and Maintain exists website.
- To do and Maintained Apis facebook messenger, like, share.

Project Terra ebook (Solo Projects)

- Create new source and Maintained website.
- Connect with customer using third party (Slack).
- To do show information about customer's rules etc.
- To do language switcher.

Project Tienphat CRM

- Fix bugs generate PDF invoices.
- To do more template invoices, bank e-invoice.
- Troubleshoot and Maintain exists website.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

District 9, Thu Duc City HCMC +0938863878 nghia.nvt291@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Back-end Developer

CLOUD TEAM COMPANY LIMITED

May 2019 - May 2022

Project Tienphat App

- Study and apply notification
- · Study and apply firebase messaging
- Troubleshoot and Maintain theme in exists app.

TECHICAL SKILLS

 Php/Laravel, Apache, Wamp, Jquery, Html, Css, Bootstrap 4, Restful Api, Design Database, Gitlab, Flutter, Wordpress

EDUCATION

Software Engineer 2017 - 2019

FPT Aptech

INTERESTS

- · Study something new
- Training
- Teambuilding
- Tea break
- Badminton
- Running
- Travel
- Music
- · Reading Book